<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content"><channel><title>Brenda Lau</title><description>Articles and devlogs.</description><link>brendalaupg.github.io</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 21:24:21 +0800</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 21:24:21 +0800</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="brendalaupg.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">brendalaupg.github.io/life/01-forward</guid><title>Forward</title><description>Looking forward to 2021.</description><link>brendalaupg.github.io/life/01-forward</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Forward</h1><p>The past few years have felt like a roller coaster. I felt the rush after reaching my highest point, descending downward until I crash and burn. I’ve struggled to get back up on my feet so many times, but I always ended up in the same place. In that place was where I threw away the mindset that drove me here. But it’s the same place where I found the courage to forgive myself. I felt that this was what I needed. For the first time in a long time, I have a fresh start. No expectations; with only one question in my mind, “Where do you want to go?”</p><p>It’s easy to look at what others have and believe you want the same things. I’ve felt this way for a long time - thinking “If I did this, then I’ll be happy” or “If I got that job, then I’ll be successful as them.” But at some point, I realized that I don’t want to be living someone else’s life or chasing someone else’s dream - I want to be living in mine.</p><p>I did a lot of self-reflection, wondering what I really wanted to do. I spent days researching my options, and I decided to pursue my Master’s degree to specialize in Artificial Intelligence. There were many sleepless nights, wondering if I’m making the wrong decision. But I found clarity within myself after re-reading my intentions for this year and explaining it to my closes friends of this decision.</p><p>My journey ahead is as scary and uncertain as ever - but I want to take this leap of faith and seize this opportunity - knowing that this is what I want for myself. When I feel like giving up, I want to come back to this post and remind myself why.</p><p>It’s a little late, but happy twenty-twenty one! I’m looking forward to what comes my way :)</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">brendalaupg.github.io/articles/01-welcome</guid><title>Welcome!</title><description>Nice seeing you here!</description><link>brendalaupg.github.io/articles/01-welcome</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Welcome!</h1><p>Hey there, welcome to my blog! There's nothing much going on at the moment, but stay tuned :)</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>